<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="defualt_help_title">Default Return</string>
    <string name="help_title_home_page">Home Page</string>
    <string name="help_title_choose_workout_plan">Choose a Workout Plan</string>
    <string name="help_title_new_workout_plan">Start a new Workout Plan</string>
    <string name="help_title_exercise_page">Exercise Page</string>
    <string name="help_title_add_exercise">Exercise Page – Add Exercise</string>
    <string name="help_title_view_exercise_stats">View Exercise - stats</string>
    <string name="help_title_log_exercise_data">Exercise Page - log data</string>
    <string name="help_title_progress_charts">Progress charts</string>
    <string name="help_title_view_workouts_and_exercises">View Workouts and exercises</string>
    <string name="help_title_edit_profile_page">Edit Profile Page</string>
    <string name="help_title_progress_graph_page">Edit Profile Page</string>

    <string name="default_help_content">Default Return</string>
    <string name="help_content_home_page">If your home screen is unpopulated, head to the Workout Screen and create a new Workout Plan.
        \nOnce your workout plans are created the home screen will be populated with all the workouts with exercises that you will have to do at that day. </string>
    <string name="help_content_choose_workout_plan">If there are no active workouts visible, select the start Workout button to create a new workout plan.
\nIf your screen is populated this means you have active workout cards available this is identifiable by the progression bar not being completed.
        \nInactive workouts have completed progress bars and will not show on this but instead can be found on the view workout and exercises screen. </string>
    <string name="help_content_new_workout_plan">Enter your workout name and description to create a new workout.
\nExample:
\n
\nChest and Shoulders
\n
\n
\nLalalala chest and shoulders at virgin active gateway </string>
    <string name="help_content_exercise_page">
If your exercise screen is unpopulated select the start exercise button to add a new exercise.
\nIf your screen is populated you can view your exercises for that workout and be able log time completed for that exercise</string>
    <string name="help_content_add_exercise">On the Add exercise screen you have the option to choose or take a progress photo, you can enter the exercise name, exercise description, date of the exercise, start and end time of the exercise, daily min/max goal and an exercise category with the options of cardio, core, arms, back, chest or legs. These will be the fields to add a new exercise to the chosen workout. </string>
    <string name="help_content_view_exercise_stats">Here you can view your exercises with a visual format, it will display the exercise date, a tick or cross if you have completed the exercise, the time it took to complete the exercise.\nThe category and the stats, you can also edit or delete the exercise.</string>
    <string name="help_content_log_exercise_data">Here you can log an exercise with the time it took to complete the exercise. You can view the exercise name and the daily min / max goals. </string>
    <string name="help_content_progress_charts">Here you can view 2 progress visualisation charts ( Daily Progress chart and Monthly Progress chart).
\nDaily progress chart requires user input of a date range to display a bar chart of the daily minimum goal.
\n
\nThe monthly progress chart displays all days where the user logged a daily time that was between the daily min / max goals with a tick in the form of a calendar chart</string>
    <string name="help_content_view_workouts_and_exercises">Here users will choose between workouts or exercises and a date range to view (active / inactive) workouts or exercises between the desired date range. If workouts are chosen the total hours of logged time will be displayed </string>
    <string name="help_content_edit_profile_page">The Edit profile screen is used to change information details pertaining to you. Here you can add a profile picture, change you Name and Surname, set gender and birthday </string>
    <string name="help_content_progress_graph_page">This is the Progress Chart Page where you can Select a Date Range and view:
\nA Bar graph of your Daily Progress with the Total hours, Total Minimum and Maximum Goals and total Daily Time.
\nA Monthly Progress Calendar that shows all the days you have met you daily fitness goal in that specific month.
\nA Pie Chart that displays percentage of workouts done or not done for each day for a month.
</string>
</resources>
